his state is sending him to Ivo again,
его государство опять отправляет на Иво
your salary is dripping, salary
тебе капают зарплата
Hello, Hello, I’m from the city of
Здравствуйте Здравствуйте я из города
Khmelnitsk, where are you from, the
Хмельницке вы откуда
girl from Moscow is a Muscovite, a native or
девушка Москвы москвичка коренная или
a newcomer,
понаехавшая
no, a
нет коренная
native, and the World Cup you communicate t in the
корена а ЧМ общаетесь т в
entrance yes About everything, let’s
летке да О всём давайте давайте
talk about life
поговорим о жизни
Let’s
Давайте
neres, you can change it and you can wear it on your shirt  you
нерес её можно сменить и ва на рубашке
can also change it a little and
его тоже немного можно
also adjust it. It
поменять сись тоже подкорректировать
is advisable to go out the entrance not to
Желательно чтобы выходить летку не
scare people, but with my height, with my
пугать людей вот при моём росте при моём
build
телосложений
and
и
90B, so 165 weight And
90Б так 165 вес А рост
what height is 107 Well, 165 and I think this is the weight you
какой 107 Ну 165 а я думаю это вес вы
said And height 165 and weight then what is
сказали А рост 165 а вес тогда какой у
my height  165 Yes, and my weight, my height is 165, and
меня ро 165 Да а вес рост у меня 165 а
my weight is 60 kg, this will suit Zhirnova for
вес у меня 60 кг это устроит жирнова для
maybe a little bit, maybe it’s a You can stand up so that
немножко може может это а Можете встать
I can, well, evaluate it visually, whether it’s wife
чтобы я ну Оценил визуально или женова
or
или
not What that You can stand up so that I can
нет Что что Можете встать чтобы я вот
look, compare height and build, not me.  I’m
посмотрел сравнил рост и комплекции не я
not
так не
filming like that, I’m not filming just so I can
снимаюсь так не сниматься просто чтобы я
look and it really matches the
посмотрел и действительно соответствует
stated weight. Well, it corresponds to what you do
заявленному Ну соответствует то что не
n’t see on the camera, I don’t see it, I see a piece of you, you
видите по камере не вижу я я кусок вас
don’t get into the camera completely,
вижу вы полностью в камеру не
I’m definitely not fat, you can already see it from your
попадаете я точно не толстая там уже по
hands, and Size,
рукам видно а Размер
what size of what? Well  the size of what
какой размер чего Ну размер того о чём
we were
мы
talking about breasts
говорили груди
Yes, the volume is
Да объём
90B this is your husband whining child Yes this is
90Б это у вас муж скули тый ребёнок Да
three rubles - This is what three children or a
трёшек - Это что такое три ребёнка или
three-year-old
трёхлетний
child is this three three children ri reb what are
ребёнок это трёх три ребёнка ри реб что
three children doing there
у вас делает три ребёнка там
right there They go to bed for a while I understand And
прямо Они немного спать ложатся понял А
who  they are put to
кто их ложит
bed by my eldest son the eldest son of the lodge And what is
Спать мой старший сын старший сын ложи А
my husband doing And I don’t have a husband
делает А у меня нет мужа
that I don’t have a husband understood yes And what happened to him he
что у меня нет мужа понял да А что с ним
left and didn’t
случилось с уехал и не
come Why
приехал Почему
isn’t he coming? What direction is
е приедет не фак На каком направлении
he in? Where is he there? Avdeevka Zaporozhye
он Где он там Авдеевка Запорожье
bakhmut  Well, I don’t know such things. Well, okay,
бахмут Ну я такие вещи не знаю Ну хорошо
for example, I met one woman on
я вот например встречал одну женщину в
chatroulette with two children. Yes, she
чатрулетке с двумя детьми Да тоже она
also said
тоже говорила муж на сво
that her husband was so happy. No, I’m saying that I met that
радостна Не а я говорю встречал что двое
there were two, and a week later I meet her. She
было да и через неделю встречаю Она
says that her husband was
говорит мужа
killed, she cried so much, I just sobbed.  I don’t
убили плакала так рыдала Просто я не
know Well, I’m saying Well, damn it, it happens like this, like, is it a
знаю Ну я говорю Ну блин ну бывает такое
war? Putin is a damn [ __ ], they
типа это ж война она ли Путин [__] блин
said that everything will be fine there.
говорили что там всё будет нормально
In short, they still haven’t made payments to her,
Короче ещё выплаты до сих пор ей не
and Putin can say that
сделали так и Путин может сказать что
everything will be fine. Putin is not a fortune teller for you.
всё будет нормально Путин не гадалка вам
Well, okay.  Now, if your husband
Ну хорошо а вот если если вам мужа Там
gets shot there or a missile
застрелят на сво да или там ракета
comes to him, what kind of compensation will you get
прилетит ему какая компенсация будет вам
as three children of a
как трх детй
mother 12 ml 12 million understood And it depends
матери 12 мл 12 млн понял А это зависит
on the number of children or
от количества детей или
simply no it’s just 12 million and
просто нет это просто 12 млн а
it turns out Well, where will you go I
получается Ну а куда вы их
’ll give them away  where will I go? Well, how are the children
денетесь отдам куда я дену Ну как дети
still small? Well, what are you doing with these 12
ещё маленькие Ну что вы с этими 12
million? Inflation will eat them up. I’ll
миллионами делаете их инфляция сожрёт я
build them cottages at home with this money.
им построю на эти деньги коттеджи дома
I’ll find something else. Where to put it? How much does
ещё что-то я найду Куда деть А сколько
one kajik
один каджик
cost? What What? How much does one kajik cost to
Стоит Что Что Сколько один катеж стоит
build? Well, if you do it yourself  build Well,
построить Ну если самому строить Ну
three million That is, it turns out
миллиона три То есть это получается
Four cottages can be stirred up Yes, yes, yes, I
Четыре котеджа можно замутить Да с
understand from the husband, that is, three types of cottage for the children,
мужа да да понял то есть три типа детям
one Kadzhik I’ll still have one for myself Well, well, it’s
котеджа один каджик Ещё себе останется
possible and it’s cool like that. And if you
Ну ну можно и так прикольно А если ещё
scroll through one more husband, you’ll have time for
одного мужа прокрутить успеть за время с
another type of four Kata in time  In general, I’ll
ещё типа на четыре Ката Я вообще я
actually be a millionaire, which is cool, damn,
вообще буду миллионер кой прикольно блин
and there are no restrictions on how many husbands
а там нет ограничений сколько мужей в
are paid per year, I can scroll on you, I’m
год выплачивается зни Я может на вас
interested in your business model, I don’t
интересно ваша бизнес-модель я вот не
sing, but in Russia there are restrictions,
пою а в России там есть ограничения
for example, per year. How many times can you
например за год Сколько раз можно за
get a payment for a husband? Well  how many times
мужа выплату получить Ну сколько раз
can you marry and send to your
можно жениться и отправить на своего
husband endlessly yes The main thing is that
мужа бесконечно да Главное чтоб
the coffee machine can withstand
кофемашина выдержала
Yes the main thing is that they get married get married understand yes and this is
Да главно чтоб женились женились понял
your husband the first second what is
да а это муж у вас первый второй какой
he the only one there are three from him Yes
он единственный пер это трое от него Да
children
детей
Yes the youngest and the eldest 18p understood yes And
Да младшему п старшему 18п понял да А
how do you-  then I wanted to
вам как-то хотелось уже муженька
change my husband
поменять
a little, well, if you sing, I’ll think about it, I don’t
немножко ну если ты поь Я подумаю не
have a husband who’s not happy with something,
име муж уже чем ну чем-то не устраивает
I see, yes, I’d like to change my husband,
я вижу да Вот хотелось бы поменять мужа
really. Why isn’t he just happy with him?
правда Почему не устраивает просто с он
He’s a defender of my Motherland, he’s
шная Он защитник моей Родины он у меня
great for my children, he’s  I have a smart girl, a smart girl, a smart
молодец моих детей он у меня умничка
guy, I understand, I understand. But
умничка шикарный мужчи понял понял А вот
look here this question. I heard
смотрите тут такой вопрос Я слышал такое
that in some regions, instead of a cash
что в некоторых регионах вместо денежной
payment, they gave a white Lada car. Is it
выплаты давали автомобиль белую Ладу это
true, or is it actually paid in money?
правда или всё-таки деньгами выплачивают
No, this is a fake, that is,
Нет это фейк ф то есть за мёртвого мужа
they give money for a dead husband, not
дают именно деньги не
Lada  for a dead husband they give exactly 12 million,
Ладу за мёртвого мужа дают именно 12 млн
how do you know that these are
откуда вы знаете что это
fairies? Because
фей Потому
because many people in Russia have already
что потому что уже много в России же по
died and died. How is it in Ukraine and
умирали помирай Как у вас в Украине а у
you have some friends who have already
вас какие-то есть знакомые которые уже
received, well, in fact, someone received 12
получили ну реально кто-то получил 12
million?  Do you have any acquaintances, do you really
млн У вас есть знакомые е реально вы
know anyone who received these 12
знаете хоть кого-то кто получил эти 12
million, if it’s not
млн если это не
fake, do you have friends who
Фейк есть у вас есть знакомые которые
received 12
получили 12
million? Yes, I understand, where
млн Да понял а куда они Дели например
did they go?
продали детей как успели построить дома
so
так
quickly the folder their well done yes our houses
быстро папка их молодец да у нас дома
are being built Lord
строятся Господи
for six months And when the folder died there that
полгода А когда папка умер там тот что
girl already received 12 ml that
девушка
Dad died that his friend of yours Get
Папа умер что его ваша знакомая Получи
12 ml has already built a house Well, I think
12 мл уже домик построила Ну я думаю в
within a month They receive this money and
течение месяца Они получают эти деньги и
then they  not when this acquaintance’s
потом они не когда вот это знакомый умер
husband died in
муж в
his acquaintance’s husband
сво знакомый муж
died a year ago a year ago in a year it
умер год назад год наза за годик уже
was already possible to build then she built
можно было построить то она построила
how many houses she
сколько она домиков
built she
построила
didn’t get paid
не е выплатили
Oh well and your husband went on his way a long time ago
Да ну и А ваш муж давно на сво
that again your husband When he went to  I
пошёл что ещё раз ваш муж Когда Пошёл на
understood it from the very beginning, that is, both my
сво с самого начала понял то есть и у
girlfriend from the very beginning and you from
подружки с самого начала и у вас с
the very beginning. But she’s luckier,
самого начала Но ей повезло больше
yes. Well, I’m luckier. I’m still alive. Well,
да Ну мне повезло больше мо пока жив Ну
he’s going to die all night like And money like
да он всю ночь умрёт типа А деньги типа
the sooner the better, but my husband is still  and
чем быстрее тем лучше но мой муж ещё и в
fought in other Wars, so I just need
других Войнах воевал поэтому мне просто
building materials like they are getting more expensive
стройматериалы типа они дорожают с
every day So it’s better Damn and my
каждым днём Так что лучше Блин а мой
Thank God will come back And when did you
Слава Богу вернётся А вы когда когда
see him The last time I heard him
видели его Последний раз я его слышу
every day and saw him live when was the
каждый день а видели вживую когда
last
последний
time 2 months ago he
раз 2 месяца назад он что
came of course  I understand, like a vacation
приезжал конечно понял а типа отпуска
there, to come there to cheer up my wife, yes, yes, I
там приехать там жену взбодрить да да
understand, yes, it’s cool to check out
понял да прикольно проверить там
how they have vacations there, like in the army for
как у них есть отпуски как в армии для
us. Oh, this is a regular army, a regular army, I
нас О это обычная армия обычная армия
understand. And who is he in the army there, a pilot? Who is
Поня А кем он армия там лётчик Кто
he
он
then, I can’t
зат я не могу
find out exactly anywhere, but  just Well, he’s a
скать именно не нигде а просто Ну вот он
tank pilot, I just
лётчик танкист просто я вот это не
don’t understand this there. I don’t understand who
понимаю там Я не разбираюсь во кем
he is in the ordinary infantry, I understood, and there, uh, they
он в обычной пехоте понял а там ээ
heard, just in case,
слышали на всякий случай ему вот
tell him next time there’s such a
расскажите в следующий раз есть такая
program, I want to live, in case he’s in short,
программа хочу жить вдруг он короче
there’ll be a very strong starship there.
будет там звездолет очень сильный так
you can contact the
можно выйти
Ukrainian special services and they take him out
на украинские спецслужбы и они выводят
onto the territory of Ukraine so they formalize it as an
на территорию Украины так оформляют Как
official prisoner of war, that is, they don’t
официально военнопленный то есть они не
say that it was he who got in touch,
говорят что это он типа вышел на связь
and then they exchange him
Да и потом ещ и нормально обменивает его
back normally. That is, it turns out that he is listed as a
назад Вот то есть получается Он числится
prisoner of war, all compensation is given, yes, it’s
военнопленным все компенсации дают да
normal  they treat him
типа нормально с ним обходятся
called I want to live program pass on
называется хочу жить программа передайте
Ukraine there are normal prisoners of war there are
украи есть нормальные военнопленные есть
also normal prisoners of war and yours, in
тоже нормальные военнопленные и ваша
short, a bunch of
короче куча
normals are cutting off no one is cutting off yet
нормаль отрезает ещё никто не отрезает
Look, this is specially done by yours such
Смотри это специально ваши делают такие
fakes so that in short yours don’t surrender from
фейки чтобы короче ваши не сдавали из
captivity but die, you understand. But it’s beneficial for you
плен а умирали понимаешь Вот Но тебе ж
Look no  so that he dies now
выгодно Смотри не чтобы он сейчас умер
Yes And so that he stays in captivity so the
Да А чтоб он Побыл в плену так за него
state makes payments for him, makes you
выплаты государство делает делает тебе
then they exchange him, the state
потом его обменивают его государство
again sends him to the vault, your salary is dripping, the
опять отправляет на свод тебе капают
salary is then already when
зарплата зарплата потом уже его когда
they kill him Yes, it will already be 12 lyams, that is, it is
грохнут Да уже 12 лямов будет то есть
necessary from your own so that not immediately  they
надо с сво чтобы не сразу грохнули
just banged 12 lyams, yes, and so you can, look at
просто 12 лямов да а так можно е смотри
the year, for example, by mining, it’s every month,
год например по майнить это каждый месяц
like the salary drips and then 12 types of
типа зарплата капает а потом 12 типа
vacation pay like that,
отпускные типа такие
my husband hardly gets it. Of course,
получаются моего мужа вряд ли Т конечно
this is the
это
time. Well, why is the very first thing I’ll
раз Ну почему самое первое что я вам
tell you that of course, no
скажу что конечно никакую
prisoner of war in Ukraine for sure  he won’t
военнопленный Украины точно не
give up, he’s ready without without without everything, he’ll blow
сдаст готов при без без без всего себе
up some dill and hit himself with
взорвёт какого-то укропа и вьёт себя
a grenade from the beginning, so it’s clear he’ll
гранатой из начала так понятно он себе
tear off his balls, he’ll tear off the grenades, I understand for the sake of your 12 million.
яйца оторвёт гранаты понял ради 12 млн
Miy Telegram directly at once he and
мий Telegram прям зараз он а
popk ce more and more respectfully YouTube keeping
попк це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us busy through skarg Orcs in your ban and even
нас через скарг Орки в твый бан и дуже
more video I don’t show people immediately I don’t
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams for that for that
показуе информация про стримы тому для
purpose for Mali operational link
того щоб ми Мали оперативный звязок
to write directly at once and while there in Telegra
пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в телегра
okm vdeo ezh tezh tsikava and korisna
окм вдео ще теж цикава и корисна
information and mi povinni z you trimati lenten
информация и ми повинни з вами тримати
operational connection
постный оперативный звязок
nezalezhno in togo chi show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Glory to Ukraine
YouTube Слава Украине
subscribe
подпишись